<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>advice on Reflections by M Hadi</title>
    <link>https://mhadi.blog/tags/advice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in advice on Reflections by M Hadi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mhadi.blog/tags/advice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sins can be like Samosas</title>
      <link>https://mhadi.blog/posts/samosas-and-sins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhadi.blog/posts/samosas-and-sins/</guid>
      <description>I was at someone&amp;rsquo;s house the other day. We were sitting at the table eating lunch, and were discussing different cuisines. The host started describing their love for Indian food, and brought up Samosas. He started telling us a story of how some years back, he ate some Samosas. It&amp;rsquo;s a good story.
It was the Islamic month of Ramadan, where Muslims don&amp;rsquo;t eat or drink during the day for 30 days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on swearing and baby steps (they&#39;re related)</title>
      <link>https://mhadi.blog/posts/swearing-and-baby-steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhadi.blog/posts/swearing-and-baby-steps/</guid>
      <description>I was considering whether or not to write this. I currently have maybe thirty more imporant things to do. But maybe someone will find this story interesting. Could be you. This is a personal reflection on swearing and baby steps. Trust me, they&amp;rsquo;re related.
Swearing is interesting. A set of words that you&amp;rsquo;re never supposed to use. But everyone uses them anyways. They&amp;rsquo;re bad, but at the same time you&amp;rsquo;re cool for using them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Question everything, but be open to learning</title>
      <link>https://mhadi.blog/posts/question-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 18:13:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhadi.blog/posts/question-everything/</guid>
      <description>Everyone around you is right. People older than you know what they&amp;rsquo;re doing. You&amp;rsquo;re just a kid - you don&amp;rsquo;t know anything, so just accept what everyone around you says. Stop asking questions!
Unfortunately, this is the mindset sometimes forced upon the young, that questioning is wrong. We&amp;rsquo;re told to accept what we hear and see.
This mindset is completely wrong, but there&amp;rsquo;s a balanece to it to. Let me explain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing for an audience vs. writing for the sake of writing</title>
      <link>https://mhadi.blog/posts/writing-for-audience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhadi.blog/posts/writing-for-audience/</guid>
      <description>Start writing I spent five years creating all sorts of content. I edited promotional videos. I took pictures of nature. I designed posters for events. I planned YouTube videos. I experimented with all sorts of things, but there was always one thing I avoided. Writing.
Why, I honestly don&amp;rsquo;t know, but there was always a fear in the back of my mind that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t good at it. I used to have some sort of notion in my mind that humans can only be good at certain things, and that I should focus my skills on other forms of creative work.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
