<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tweets on Reflections by M Hadi</title>
    <link>https://mhadi.blog/tags/tweets/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tweets on Reflections by M Hadi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 13:52:56 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mhadi.blog/tags/tweets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ideas can be painkillers, vitamans, or candies</title>
      <link>https://mhadi.blog/posts/painkillers-vs-vitamans-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 13:52:56 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhadi.blog/posts/painkillers-vs-vitamans-ai/</guid>
      <description>Tony Fadell described how the best ideas are painkillers, not vitamins.
A painkiller solves a major issue. Something wrong. A problem that shouldn&amp;rsquo;t exist.
A vitamin is an addition. It enhances you. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t solve a problem, it assists a solution.
With the rise of AI, most new ideas aren&amp;rsquo;t even vitamins anymore, let along painkillers.
They&amp;rsquo;re candies.
Soely for the purpose of enjoyment.
Is your idea a painkiller?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life is about perspectives</title>
      <link>https://mhadi.blog/posts/life-is-about-perspectives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 13:52:56 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhadi.blog/posts/life-is-about-perspectives/</guid>
      <description>The sound designer says to start w/ music and have video flow it.
The video editor says to start w/ footage and have music flow to it.
The sound designer hates the video editor. The video editor hates the sound designer.
&amp;ldquo;They don&amp;rsquo;t understand me.&amp;rdquo;
Two sides of the same story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on productive procrastination</title>
      <link>https://mhadi.blog/posts/productive-procrastination/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 13:52:56 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhadi.blog/posts/productive-procrastination/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Productive procrastination&amp;rdquo; - it&amp;rsquo;s a term I learnt from screenwriter Rodney Rothman. A term that changed how I see work and could change how you see it too.
In an interview with Jeff Goldsmith, Rothman says “my habits are pretty neurotic, I find I do this very productive procrastination these days… I’ll do research, I’ll make notes, I’ll draw weird maps of ideas, like diagram the story in some weird way that only I understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on reading</title>
      <link>https://mhadi.blog/posts/reflections-on-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 13:52:56 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhadi.blog/posts/reflections-on-reading/</guid>
      <description>For two years, I thought reading was the nerdiest thing in the world.
From an early age, I was obsessed with reading, but I would only read fiction. I thought that non-fiction was extremely boring and completely useless.
Until the age of 14, I would read around 100 books every year, probably even more. From mystery to adventure, reading served as my substitute for watching movies.
Then, one day, I stopped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The drafts</title>
      <link>https://mhadi.blog/posts/the-drafts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhadi.blog/posts/the-drafts/</guid>
      <description>Half written, half baked. Coming soon to a full post near you&amp;hellip; or not. The following are a collection of drafts.
Ideas AI The anti-ai revolution AI vs creativity - the backlash thats coming especially for AI art AI killing creativity, worst thing to use AI for is a blog outsourcing personality for AI Issue with AI art Other You don’t need social media - story of snapchat
Overdeliver on projects to continue working</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
