<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>story on Reflections by M Hadi</title>
    <link>https://mhadi.blog/tags/story/</link>
    <description>Recent content in story on Reflections by M Hadi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 13:52:56 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mhadi.blog/tags/story/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Life is about perspectives</title>
      <link>https://mhadi.blog/posts/life-is-about-perspectives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 13:52:56 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhadi.blog/posts/life-is-about-perspectives/</guid>
      <description>The sound designer says to start w/ music and have video flow it.
The video editor says to start w/ footage and have music flow to it.
The sound designer hates the video editor. The video editor hates the sound designer.
&amp;ldquo;They don&amp;rsquo;t understand me.&amp;rdquo;
Two sides of the same story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sins can be like Samosas</title>
      <link>https://mhadi.blog/posts/samosas-and-sins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhadi.blog/posts/samosas-and-sins/</guid>
      <description>I was at someone&amp;rsquo;s house the other day. We were sitting at the table eating lunch, and were discussing different cuisines. The host started describing their love for Indian food, and brought up Samosas. He started telling us a story of how some years back, he ate some Samosas. It&amp;rsquo;s a good story.
It was the Islamic month of Ramadan, where Muslims don&amp;rsquo;t eat or drink during the day for 30 days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Cinematic Leap into Imagination: Across the Spider-Verse</title>
      <link>https://mhadi.blog/posts/cinematic-storytelling-of-across-the-spiderverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 20:46:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhadi.blog/posts/cinematic-storytelling-of-across-the-spiderverse/</guid>
      <description>The following is adapted from a research paper I wrote for a college course. Originally meant to be five pages, it ended up being nineteen by the time I finished writing all my thoughts. Enjoy the blood, sweat, and tears that went into this. WARNING: SPOILERS AHEAD.
For the longest time, animations have tried to mimic real-life imagery through their lighting, framing, characters, and setting. But what happens when animators break that boundary?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
